{"data":[{"question":"If airplane ticket wasn't expensive, I could fly to Singapore for my holidays.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"If","b":"wasn't","c":"could fly","d":"for","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Wasn't -> weren't","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Friends advised her to stop doing the housework because her old age.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"her","b":"to stop","c":"housework","d":"because","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Because-> because of","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Although she is 103 but she still does a lot of work in the flat.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Although","b":"is","c":"but","d":"a lot of","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- But->x,","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"He had so a difficult exercise that he couldn't do it.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"had","b":"so","c":"difficult","d":"it","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- So-> such","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"It is the larger city in Europe with a population of over eight million.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"larger","c":"in","d":"of","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n-Larger-> largest","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"It is a beautiful building of two towers and a very big clock called Big Ben.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"beautiful","b":"of","c":"very","d":"called","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Beautiful-> more beautiful","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Many hundred years ago there were many villages and little towns in England.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"ago","b":"were","c":"little","d":"in","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Little-> few\/a few","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"They usually took a tree back with them and put it on the centre of the village.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"with","b":"put","c":"on","d":"of","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- On-> at","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"The international working class made the one of May their day of solidarity.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"working","b":"made","c":"one","d":"of","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- One-> first","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"The first May Day celebrated in England in 1890.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"first","b":"celebrated","c":"in","d":"1890","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Celebrated-> was celebrated","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"}]}